He's watching your six.
Sniper: Special Ops is a action, war film directed by Fred Olen Ray.
A Special Ops military Force, led by expert sniper Sergeant Jake Chandler, are sent to a remote
Afghan village to extract an American congressman being held by the Taliban.
Sergeant Jake Chandler, played by Steven Seagal.
Sergeant Victor 'Vic' Thomas Mosby, played by Tim Abell.
Vasquez, played by Rob Szatkowski.
Lieutenant Colonel Jackson, played by Dale Dye.
Janet Conrad, played by Charlene Amoia.
Tyler, played by Jason-Shane Scott.
Sniper Special Ops is a 2016 American war action drama film written and directed by Fred Olen Ray
and starring Steven Seagal, who also serves as executive producer for the film.
It is unrelated to the long-running Sniper film series.